

MARCHENDA FAYZA MADJID

Student at Information Technology, Faculty of Computer Science, Brawijaya University

PROFILE

I've experience in Graphic Design ever since High School and also learn about programming since 2018. Currently, I'm focusing myself on Software Development, such as Web and Mobile Development including UI/UX Designer.

I want to create many new experiences, meet new people and learn new things. I like to help others and keep the hardwork to be an agile, grit and strive to be an excellent person. I also enjoy new challenges that enable me to arow.

CONTACT

+62 831 2921 7353

marchendafayzam@gmail.com

im linkedin.com/in/marchendafayzam

fay.loveu

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia Native English Intermediate Japanese Beginner

SKILLS Graphic Design

Adobe Photoshop, Figma Advanced Adobe Illustrator Intermediate

Programming

HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, MySQL, Bootstrap, Laravel Advanced

Javascript, Git Intermediate

Kotlin Beginner

EDUCATION

2019 - Now

Student on Information System Major, at the Faculty of Computer Science, Brawijaya University

NIM: 195150700<mark>111025</mark>

2016-2019

Student at SMA Negeri 1 Balikpapan

PUBLICATIONS/BOOKS

Author of Sekeping Logam Sejuta Cerita Publish by Deepublish, 2018

ACHIEVEMENTS

August, 2021

1st Place in UI/UX Competition

Held by HMP PTI Muhammadiyah Surakarta University, Surakarta, Indonesia

July, 2021

3rd Place in ITC CONVERT 2021 UI/UX Competition Held by HIMASIF Jember University, Jember, Indonesia

November, 2020

Finalist of Business Plan Workshop & Competition 2020 Held by Tanoto Foundation

EXPERIENCES

Organization

2021 - Now

Head of Secretary and Treasurer

at Association of Information Technology Students (KBMTI FILKOM UB)

Member of Internal Department

at Tanoto Scholars Association Universitas Brawijaya

2020 - 2021

Member of Advocacy Department

at Association of Information Technology Students (KBMTI FILKOM UB)

Member of External Department

at Tanoto Scholars Association Universitas Brawijaya

Member of Biostra Department

at BIOS FILKOM UB

Training/Volunteership

November 2021 - Now

Lead Others Camp TELADAN 2021

Held by Tanoto Foundation

November 2021

#TechSeries Workshop: Koltlin 101

Held by Google Developer Student Clubs UB

January - February 2020

Lead Self Camp TELADAN 2020

Held by Tanoto Foundation

